iOS Engineer OHN LIMA

thejohnlima@icloud.com

â

https://linkedin.com/in/thejohnlima

thejohnlima

EXPERIENCE

FreeCast Inc

iOS | tvOS Engineer | January 2021 - December 2023

Working with Swift for iOS and tvOS apps

PagSeguro UOL

iOS Engineer | July 2018 - March 2021

Working with native apps using Swift

Stormbreaker Studios

iOS Developer | January 2020 - December 2020

Working in iOS apps using Swift

BRQ

iOS Developer | April 2017 - June 2018

Working with native apps using Swift and Objective-C

Magna Sistemas

iOS Developer | February 2016 - April 2017

Working with native apps using Swift

Urban Summer

iOS Developer | March 2015 - February 2016

Working with native and hybrid apps

EDUCATION

Learning algorithms, software engineer, databases, software development in FMU, Sao Paulo, Brazil

System Analysis and Development | February 2014 - June 2018

Learning a lot of concepts about iOS development in Impacta, Sao Paulo, Brazil

About me

I'm passionate about technology, science, developing things that improve people's lives and make the world a better place. I've been working with mobile development for iOS platform since 2014 with experience on all steps of iOS development, from the concept ofthe ideas until releasing the app on the store and following the results with analytics, tests and crashreports.